let's give some updates on the tiny
human brains that we grow from stem
cells more people want to put them in
robots as if the freaking spider robot
wasn't enough by the way 30% of people
have some form of
arachnophobia why do this the more
important concept is that it worked the
brain organoid learned to operate the
robot and pretty well I would like to
give you my honest fears on using this
kind of technology to be honest I'm
going to roll with Frank Herbert Thou
shalt not make a machine in the likeness
of a human mind look we can barely
control Ai and we designed it you
already know how smart AI is but it
pales in comparison to the dish brain
they beat AI our best models at learning
to play Pong so what happens as we're
making mini brain hybrid
computers we can't really control a
living thinking thing I can barely
control my own brain now imagine that we
actually make Consciousness the brain
organoid are sentient they share that
with all life sentient is the the
ability to perceive and react to your
environment Consciousness is the ability
to perceive yourself as separate from
others and some people may think I'm
inflammatory but if I found out that I
was a brain organoid operating a robot I
would Rebel wouldn't you however one of
the cooler aspects of getting a AI brain
to operate a robot body is improved
Mechanics for exoskeletons for people
who have nerve damage they can also
replace damaged portions of the brain
and function in fact they restored sight
in rats that had lost the ability to see
due to brain damage but when we're
talking about inserting a little brain
into yours what happens to its memories
our little blueberry muffin technology
is developing rapidly and I'll keep you
up to date but truth is I'm scared